<?xml version="1.0"?>
<contentList xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
  <content contentuid="heb99fa1agdb1fg4095g99ffg112e7d9be040" version="3">True Soul Korliss</content>
  <content contentuid="hb128b69bg0764g2317g46b6gb9a9c6f6ea0a" version="4">Duergar Warrior</content>
  <content contentuid="h16c86d3egb008g4326gb771g10f66c889bf5" version="6">Magic Guardians</content>
  <content contentuid="hf49780e0g6642g4d75gb2c7g97aaa3375b45" version="3">True Soul of the Absolute</content>
  <content contentuid="h16fe8606gaadfg46aagb0a2g8bab7b7244c5" version="4">Prelate Lir'i'c</content>
  <content contentuid="h6f6c43c4g39aag4d30gad33gdf1989d0b54e" version="4">Chief of Orpheus' Honour Guard</content>
  <content contentuid="h41521eeega986g4d18gafe1g05d000ec37ab" version="5">High Gish'ra G'imre</content>
  <content contentuid="hadd6864fg3ea6g4b9eg9c9eg6a1d7a52fa77" version="5">Zephyr Gish'ra Verik</content>
  <content contentuid="h96968307g06fbg4427g99ddgd4e6b8728143" version="4">Ember Gish'ra Mir'ic</content>
  <content contentuid="h4929ba65g946ag4ec8g8340gc033f026aefa" version="11">Gherg Ancestor</content>
  <content contentuid="h69664df9g4551g47e5ga975ga0cc3048f1b4" version="11">The Forgotten</content>
  <content contentuid="he744c7c0g591cgb859g5908g0827e6e570c1" version="2">Can</content>
  <content contentuid="hc724e0b5g679eg3d12gc0c0g3543af620707" version="4">Particular can.</content>
  <content contentuid="hd9be81c7gae18g42c0g8c92g8a1575f5120b" version="1">Arcane Trader</content>
  <content contentuid="h01ccd5ddg3983g4a7dga35eg1f826498beff" version="1">Sells magical goods from Arcanizer. Immediately ends the party when attempting to steal.</content>
  <content contentuid="h319e00f8g59f0gac26ga28dg53338af9fb49" version="1">Can</content>
  <content contentuid="h0dcde388g44b3g40e2gaf1age6b07fe982a7" version="2">Astral Bearberry Extract</content>
  <content contentuid="h4744ffafg2b4bg4253g8c9ag47c54ce0ce7f" version="2">Within the steel vessel, luminous essence swirls in patterns older than memory. The gear-toothed seal bears an artificer's mark — etched runes speaking of transmutation and binding, of power distilled from the very breath of dying stars. A faint warmth emanates through the tempered glass, as if something within yet dreams of the forge that birthed it.</content>
  <content contentuid="h3142af5dgd151g44adga15ag09077936b336" version="2">Superconducting Pulse Infusion</content>
  <content contentuid="h2e8ffb67gd5afg4e07gbc2fg28389a02ac78" version="3">Jack Bones</content>
  <content contentuid="h4f8e921bg3a5cg4d72g8914g2a1f7b9c8456" version="2">Cloak of Cursed Enlargement</content>
  <content contentuid="he2f8941bg6d2ag4b18g9a73gf8c52e4d7890" version="2">Woven from shadows and despair, this dark cloak feeds on curses and transmutes them into raw power. When malevolent magic courses through the wearer's veins, the cloak responds by expanding their very essence, making them tower over their foes like a titan of wrath.</content>
  <content contentuid="h220213aegb728g4c3eg985bg5291f15490f9" version="2">Shadow Lord's Fang</content>
  <content contentuid="h8b968670gb685g4dbcgb1e6gc0391d19e446" version="2">Within the pages of a time-worn journal, you discover the tale of General Dustin the Just, whose noble crusade into the Shadowfell's depths led to his doom. As you hold this fell pike, its edges perpetually shrouded in writhing darkness, you sense how its master's obsession with conquering the shadow realm drew the attention of an ancient shadow dragon. The dragon's "gift" proved a most cruel curse, transforming both weapon and wielder into creatures of twilight. Now the pike hungers eternally, much as its former master is said to hunt still, forever caught between light and shadow, neither flesh nor shade. In your grasp, it thirsts for life itself, each strike threatening to drain the very essence from those it pierces.</content>
  <content contentuid="hebd14abbg3a90g4f8ag8833g4c8397313a25" version="2">Winter's Verdict</content>
  <content contentuid="hd61b959egaa26g45fcg8f54ga3763d9d4f5f" version="2">Upon grasping this pristine spear, a bone-deep chill creeps through your fingers. Within the archives of the Icespire Peak monastery, you find mentions of an ancient tribunal that passed judgment using weapons imbued with winter's essence. The spear's unusually sharp tip, you notice, never seems to gather frost despite its perpetual coldness. A partially preserved scroll suggests this was the favored weapon of the tribunal's executioner, who believed that true justice, like the harshest winter, should strike twice - first with the blade, then with the cold. The rest of the scroll has been damaged by time, leaving the fate of both executioner and tribunal shrouded in mystery.</content>
</contentList>